beretta.com 2015-12-09

# Privacy Policy

###  WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

Information under art. 13 of Italian Privacy law no. 196 of  30th June 2003, "Personal Data Protection Act" (hereinafter referred to as "Act").

This page explains how the website is managed with reference to the processing of the personal data of the users consulting it and data sent spontaneously by anyone visiting our website **(http://www.beretta.com** ) corresponding to the home page of the **Fabbrica d’Armi P. Beretta S.p.A.** website.

This information is not provided for other websites consulted by the user via a link.

###  THE DATA CONTROLLER

Consultation of this website  involves the processing of personal data referring to identified or identifiable subjects.  
The data controller is Fabbrica D’Armi P. Beretta S.p.A., registered office at 18, Via P. Beretta,  Gardone VT, Brescia, Italy.  

###  PLACE WHERE DATA ARE PROCESSED

Website personal data are processed at the registered office of the Data Controller and at the premises of the Provider hosting the website, and are handled by the technical staff commissioned by the Data Controller and Provider or by data handler commissioned occasionally to perform maintenance operations.

###  TYPE OF DATA HANDLED

Navigation data  
During normal operation, computer systems and software procedures used to operate this website acquire personal data, the disclosure of which is implicit when using Internet communication protocols.  
Such data are collected to be associated with identified subjects but, due to their nature,  they might allow identification of the users through associations with data held by third parties.

Data supplied voluntarily by the user  
Personal data sent voluntarily to Beretta via e-mail or on the relevant forms will be handled in accordance with the principles of correctness, lawfulness and transparency in order to safeguard the subject’s privacy and rights. These data will only be disclosed to third parties if required to supply the service requested by the user.

###  PURPOSE

The personal data acquired may be used for commercial and promotional purposes, and to compile statistics on the quality of the services rendered, to identify potential customers for each product and service, and to send – by letter, telephone, fax, automated systems, etc. – information of a technical or general nature and of a commercial and promotional nature regarding the products and services of the company or delegated subjects authorised to receive them.  
Consent to the despatch of faxes and e-mails can be expressed by entering your fax number or e-mail address in the designated fields, as shown on the data request forms.  
Personal data sent voluntarily by the subject may be disclosed to third parties, as specified on the company’s information sheet.  
Specific information in summary form will be displayed progressively on the company website covering any future services that are implemented.  

##  COOKIES

The Fabbrica d'Armi Pietro Beretta has updated its cookie policy. We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. This includes cookies from third party social media websites if you visit a page which contains embedded content from social media. Such third party cookies may track your use of the Fabbrica d'Armi Pietro Beretta website. We and our partners also use cookies to ensure we show you advertising that is relevant to you. If you continue without changing your settings,  we'll assume that you are happy to receive all cookies on the Fabbrica d'Armi Pietro Beretta websites . Learn More

###  OPTIONAL DISCLOSURE

In addition to navigation data rights, you are free to supply the personal data requested on the forms provided, and you may also send e-mails to any of the addresses given.  

###  DATA PROCESSING METHODS

Data processing will take place in compliance with art. 11 of the Data Protection Act by hand and/or with the aid of computers and telematic means. The data may be kept as hardcopy or in electronic files, for the time strictly required.  Specific security measures are adopted to prevent the loss of the data, illicit or incorrect use, and unauthorised access.  

###  COMMUNICATION AND DIFFUSION

The subject’s personal data will not be passed on to anyone else, unless the company is specifically asked by the subject to do so.  

###  SUBJECT’S RIGHTS

The subject to whom the personal data refer enjoys the rights specified in art. 7 of the Italian Data Protection Act, including the right to obtain erasure, anonymisation or blocking of data that have been processed unlawfully, and to object, on legitimate grounds, to the processing of personal data concerning him/her. Please specify in the “subject” field that the request is made pursuant to art. 7 of the Italian Data Protection Act.

Address for sending requests for erasure or rectification of personal data:

Please note that this document, published at the following address http://www.beretta.com/index.aspx?m=Privacy constitutes the “Privacy Information Note” of this web site that will be reviewed.

**Marketing Office**  
Fabbrica D’Armi P. Beretta S.p.A.  
Via P. Beretta 18 - P.O. Box 160  
25063 Gardone VT  BS  
Italy
